Let's try Mateo ice cream first.
Let's make people try our gelatos.
There is a challenge. You have two ice creams. Mine is dark chocolate,
chili peppers and honey. Mine is with lemon, olive oil
and black pepper. I know. Be open minded.
And then both. I'm really ready. Let's try Mateo ice cream first.
Flavor. I like it. He likes it. He doesn't love it. It's a unique
flavor. It's interesting in a positive way.
Said excellent. Eight out of ten. Very, very spicy.
The best two, one. I'm voting for Emiliano just
to be sure he knows. He knows we love spice.
Okay. I'm a chocolate lover. I had to go. Mateo.
Let's see.
Congratulations. Sorry, Matt. Let me try
yours. I want to try yours too. I mean, it's pretty good. It is actually
good. And the votes are even. Let's do this. They decide which one
wins. Write it in a.